Guide to the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Papers TAM.694
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. International and Domestic Events, 1956-2016, undated; 8 audiocassettes; 1 film reels; 1 VHS; 53.52 Gigabytes in 6,374 computer files.; 26.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 53 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, and 1.5 media boxes.
  - Subseries II.A. Conferences, Summits, and Forums, 1956-2015, undated; 6 audiocassettes; 1 VHS; 1 film reels; 44.58 Gigabytes in 4,704 computer files.; 18 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 29 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, and 1 media box.
    - 1993 Yeshiva University Dinner in Honor of Rabbi Arthur Schneier in Support of the Establishment of the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Chair in International Relations: Program, 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - 1993 Yeshiva University Dinner Honoring Rabbi Arthur Schneier in Support of the Establishment of the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Chair in International Relations: Report, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - 1994 Conference on Northern Ireland: Correspondence, Programs, Brochure, and Press, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - 1994 Dinner at Argentine Ambassador's Residence: Schedule and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 1994 Dinner at Argentine Washington, D.C. Embassy: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 1994 International Conference on Orthodox Religious Activities in the Commonwealth of Independent States: Program, List of Participants, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - 1994 The International Jewish/Christian Conference on Modern Social and Scientific Challenges: Program and Correspondence, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - 1994 Luncheon for Metropolitan Syridon: Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 128, Folder 9, 10)
    - 1994 Signing Ceremony of the Peace Treaty between Israel and Jordan: Photographs, Images, and Travel Instructions, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - 1994 Signing Ceremony of the Peace Treaty between Israel and Jordan: Photographs and Negatives, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - 1994 Visit to China: Photograph and Plaque for Jewish Community, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - 1994 Visit to Russia and Austria: Photographs, Images, and Negatives, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - 1994 Visit to Serbia: Photographs -- Belgrade, Serbia, 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - 1994 Yeshiva University 70th Annual Hanukkah Dinner: Program and Notes, 1 folder (Box 277, Folder 26)
    - 1995 Allied Victory in Europe Celebration in Moscow: Images, 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - 1995 Allied Victory in Europe Celebration in Moscow: Photographs and Negatives -- Various Political and Religious Leaders, 2 folders (Box 126, Folder 5, 6)
    - 1995 Balkan Conference: Video Recording (Box 275, Cassette 694.0047)
    - 1995 Conference on Genocide and Holocaust: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - 1995 Conference of Presidents of Major American Jewish Organizations: Schedule, 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - 1995 Conference of Presidents of Major American Jewish Organizations: Schedule, Correspondence, Program, and Elizabeth Schneier Name Tag, 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - 1995 United Nations 50th Anniversary Reunion of Former Public Delegates: List of Delegates, Speeches, and Folders, 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - 1995 Visit to Israel and England: Photographs -- Israel, London, Swiss Embassy, and the Presidents of Major American Jewish Organizations Conference, 2 folders (Box 127, Folder 1, 2)
    - 1996 Bosnia, a Just Peace Discussion Series: Correspondence, Schedule, and Press, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - 1996 The Mayor Dinner: Program and Speech, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 22)
    - 1996 Vienna Lectures: Poster, Correspondence, Lectures, and Brochures, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - 1996 Vienna Lectures: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - 1996 Visit to China: Itinerary, Handouts, Lists of Contacts, Schedule, and Articles -- Schneier, Elizabeth, 1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - 1996 Visit to Russia: Certificate to Observe Russian Election -- Schneier, Elizabeth, 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - 1997 The Fifth Path to Peace Award: Programs, 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 22)
    - 1997 Trip to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Correspondence and Press -- Forum of Friends of the Peace Process in Bosnia and Herzegovina, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - 1997 United States Institute of Peace Meeting for Intercommunal Relations in Bosnia-Herzegovina and Yugoslavia:, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Yeshiva University Benjamin N. Cardozo Award: Photograph, 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - 1997 Yeshiva University Benjamin N. Cardozo Award: Program, Brochure, News Releases, Awardee Biographical Information, and Speeches, 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - 1997 Yeshiva University Law School Dinner in Honor of King Juan Carlos I and Queen Sofia: Speeches, Correspondence, and Schedule, 1 folder (Box 277, Folder 25)
    - 1998 American Jewish Congress Presidential Inaugural & Isaiah Award Dinner: Program and Table Number List, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - 1998 Committee on Conscience, Genocide and Crimes Against Humanity: Information Packet, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - 1998 PES Gift of the Torah to Ohel Rachel Synagogue: Agreement, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - 1998 PES Gift of the Torah to Ohel Rachel Synagogue: Photographs -- at PES, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - 1998 Restoration of Ohel Rachel Synagogue in Shanghai: Correspondence, Press, and Floor Plans, 1995-1998; 2 folders (Box 235, Folder 11, 12)
    - 1998 Restoration of Ohel Rachel Synagogue in Shanghai: Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, Hillary Clinton, and Secretary of State Madeleine Albright, undated; 2 folders (Box 245, Folder 2, 5)
    - 1998 Restoration of Ohel Rachel Synagogue in Shanghai: Press, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Biographical Information -- Delegates, 1996-1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Briefing and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Briefings, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- with Congress, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- The Chinese Bureau of Religious Affairs, 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Delegation, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 234, Folder 17, 18)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Freedom House, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Goals of Mission, 1997; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- with Hosts, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Muslims in China, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Political Prisoner Information from the Chinese Religious Affairs Bureau, 1992; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Public Relations Firms, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Speaking Engagements, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- About Tibet, 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- U.S. Consulates and Embassy in China, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- U.S. Department of State, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 19)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- U.S.-China Business Council, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence -- Wei Jingsheng, 1992-1998; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence and Press, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 190, Folder 16, 17)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence and Press -- Public Relations Firm, 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Correspondence, Press, Report, and Photographs, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Guest List, Correspondence, Speakers Biographical Information -- Asia Society Private Briefing, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Images -- with Mr. Ye, undated; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Itineraries, Correspondence, Guest Lists, and Schedules, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Menu, Itineraries, Schedules, and Correspondence, 1998, undated; 2 folders (Box 96, Folder 19, 20)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Notes, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs, 1998, undated; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 2, Box 150, Folder 27)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs -- Meeting with President Bill Clinton at the White House, undated; 2 folders (Box 245, Folder 4, 7)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs -- Press Conference, undated; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 16)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs -- with Ambassador Richardson, undated; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs and Correspondence -- with President Jiang, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs and Images, undated; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs and Negatives, undated; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 3, 10)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Photographs and Negatives -- Visit to Tibet, undated; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Press, 21 folders (Box 233, Folder 18, Box 95, Folder 1-13, Box 96, Folder 10, Box 234, Folder 15, Box 195, Folder 2-6)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Press -- Meeting with President Clinton Pre-Trip, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Press Kit and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Prisoner Lists, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Report, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Report Drafts, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: Speeches, Correspondence, and Press -- Hearing Before Senate Finance Committee, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - 1998 U.S. Religious Leaders Delegation to China: U.S. Consulate Information, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 20)
    - 1998 Visit to China and Israel: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - 1998 Visit to China and Israel: Correspondence, Press, Name Tag, and Programs, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 17)
    - 1998 Visit to China and Israel: Itinerary and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - 1998 Visit to China and Israel: Itinerary, Notes, Press, and Correspondence, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - 1998 Visit to China and Israel: Press -- White House, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - 1998 Visit to Israel: Invitation, Travel Information, and Contacts, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - 1999 Henan Province Trade Fair: Correspondence and Photograph, 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - 1999 I Never Saw Another Butterfly Performance at PES: Press and Program, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - 1999 Meeting with President Ricardo Alarcon of the National Assembly of Cuba: Photograph, 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - 1999 Shanghai Synagogue Ohel Rachel Holds First Rosh Hashana Services: Press, 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - 1999 Visit to Austria: Correspondence, Event Program, and Folder of Handouts, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Gracie Mansion Breakfast Honoring Rabbi Arthur Schneier: Sound Recording (Box 255, Cassette 694.0025)
    - 2000 The Inauguration of the Liechtenstein Institute on Self-Determination at Princeton University: Program, Correspondence, and Press, 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - 2000 The Inauguration of the Liechtenstein Institute on Self-Determination at Princeton University: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - 2000 Jews of China Exhibit at PES: Correspondence, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 190, Folder 14, 15)
    - 2000 Orthodox Union National Rabbinic Centennial Awards Dinner: Photographs, 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - 2000 PES Dinner Dance Honoring Rabbi Arthur Schneier's 70th Birthday and Global Spiritual Leadership: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 272, Folder 5, 6)
    - 2000 PES Dinner Dance Honoring Rabbi Arthur Schneier's 70th Birthday and Global Spiritual Leadership: Speeches, Correspondence, and Press, 2 folders (Box 272, Folder 9, 10)
    - 2000 UN World Conference: Press and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - 2000 Visit to England and France: Itinerary, Correspondence, and Notes, 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - 2000 Visit to Switzerland and France: Itinerary and Correspondence -- Nestle General Assembly, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 19)
    - 2000 Zurich Leader Forum: Correspondence, Program, Itinerary, List of Participants, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 23)
    - 2001 Consecration of the Sanctuary of Central Synagogue: Brochure -- Donor List, 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Cruise to Brazil: Correspondence, Itinerary, Contacts, and Travel Information, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - 2001 Moscow Patriarchate Interreligious Conference on Peace: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - 2001 The Samuel Dorsky Symposium on Public Monuments: Printed Bound Speeches, 1 folder (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - 2001 The Samuel Dorsky Symposium on Public Monuments: Speech, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - 2001 The Samuel Dorsky Symposium on Public Monuments: Speech, Program, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - 2001 UJA Federation The Steven J. Ross Award Dinner: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Correspondence -- UN Resolution, 4 folders (Box 276, Folder 7, 8, 10, 11)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Correspondence and Press -- New York Times Advertisement, 1 folder (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Press -- UN Resolution, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Press and Correspondence -- Call to Stop the Desecration of Holy Sites, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 276, Folder 12)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Press and Speeches, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 33)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Resolutions and Press, 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Sound Recording -- Resolution for the Protection of Religious Sites (Box 255, Cassette 694.0037)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Speech and Correspondence -- Seton Hall, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - 2001 United Nations Year of Dialogue Among Civilizations: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - 2001 The University Club Lecture Luncheon: Flyer, 1 folder (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Correspondence and Brochure -- Interfaith Meeting on the Peace of God in the World, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Correspondence, Notes, and Press, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Declaration, Speech, Flyer, and Program, 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Itinerary, Notes, Programs, Correspondence, and Photographs, 2001, undated; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Press -- Interfaith Meeting on the Peace of God in the World, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Program and Speeches -- Interfaith Meeting on the Peace of God in the World, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Speech and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - 2001 Visit to Belgium, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia: Speech, Press, List of Participants -- Interfaith Meeting on the Peace of God in the World, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Visit to Liechtenstein: Program, Booklet, and Information Packet, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - 2001 Visit to Romania, Switzerland, and Germany: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Visit to Romania, Switzerland, and Germany: Itinerary, Correspondence, Report, Schedule, and Press, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - 2002 America-Israel Friendship League Dinner: Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - 2002 Committee on Conscience Symposium: Program and Travel Documents, 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 30)
    - 2002 Liechtenstein Prime Minister Visit to PES: Correspondence and Press, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - 2002 PACE University Commencement: Program, Invocation, and List of Honored Guests, 1 folder (Box 277, Folder 18)
    - 2002 United States Department of State, Secretary's Open Forum: Correspondence and Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur Delivers The 2002 Distinguished Lecture on Tolerance and Religious Freedom, 2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - 2002 United States Department of State, Secretary's Open Forum: Sound Recording -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur's Distinguished Lecture Speech (Box 255, Cassette 694.0024)
    - 2002 United States Department of State, Secretary's Open Forum: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - 2002 United States Department of State, Secretary's Open Forum: Speech, Correspondence, Calendar, Press, and Biographical Information -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur Delivers the 2002 Distinguished Lecture on Tolerance and Religious Freedom, 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Correspondence, Photograph, and Notes, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Correspondence, Schedule, and Press, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Guest Lists -- Receptions in Honor of Rabbi Arthur Schneier, 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Itinerary, Event Guest List, and Schedule, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Photographs and Negatives -- Romania, 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Photographs and Negatives -- Romania and Paris, France, 2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Press, 1 folder (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Sound Recording -- Traditions and Cultural Values in Romania (Box 255, Cassette 694.0028)
    - 2002 Visit to Romania and France: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur on Receiving a Honorary Degree from Alexandru Ioan Cuza University in Iasi, Romania, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Correspondence -- The Millennium World Peace Summit of Religious and Spiritual Leaders, 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Correspondence and Event Guest List, 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Correspondence, Information Packet, and Notes -- The Millennium World Peace Summit of Religious and Spiritual Leaders, 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 21)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Itinerary, Correspondence, and Handouts, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 1, Box 108, Folder 27)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Itinerary, Correspondence, and Travel Information, 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Photographs -- Meeting with Israeli President Moshe Katsav, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - 2002 Visit to Thailand, Israel, Switzerland, Czech Republic, and Germany: Speeches and Statement -- The Millennium World Peace Summit of Religious and Spiritual Leaders, 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - 2002 World Day of Prayer with Pope John Paul II in Assisi, Italy: Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - 2002 World Day of Prayer with Pope John Paul II in Assisi, Italy: Photographs and Photographic Film, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - 2002 World Economic Forum: Name Tag -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - 2002 World Economic Forum: Photographs -- at Ground Zero, undated; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - 2002 World Economic Forum: Photographs and Photographic Film, undated; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - 2003 A Celebration of Jewish Heritage and Culture: Program and Speech, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - 2003 Chief Israeli Rabbi Yona Metzger Visits PES: Photographs and Images, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_97
      - Prints (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - 2003 China Merchants Bank Reception: Photographs, 2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 15)
    - 2003 Chinese National Day Reception: Photograph, 2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - 2003 Dinner in Honor of Swiss Ambassador Francois Nordmann: List of Guests and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 16)
    - 2003 Dinner Hosted by South Korean United Nations Representative Kim Sam-Hoon in Honor of Rabbi Arthur Schneier: Correspondence, Guest Lists, and Handouts, 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - 2003 Dinner Hosted by South Korean United Nations Representative Kim Sam-Hoon in Honor of Rabbi Arthur Schneier: Photographs and Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - 2003 Greek Orthodox Dinner in Honor of President George H.W. Bush: Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 17)
    - 2003 Inauguration of Governor George E. Pataki: Correspondence and Benediction, 1 folder (Box 277, Folder 19)
    - 2003 International Council on Terrorism: Program, Notes and Slides, 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 8)